[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the code name of fictional character Roger Bartlett, portrayed by Richard Attenborough in the movie The Great Escape?", "correct_answer": "Big X", "incorrect_answers": ["The SBO", "The Surveyor", "The Tunneler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Bram Stokers horror novel, vampires are the henchmen of this Count.", "correct_answer": "Dracula", "incorrect_answers": ["Vlad", "Van Helsing", "Frankenstein"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Asian Elephant, the only living species of the genus Elephas, is the bigger relative of the African Elephant.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This popular board game, patented in 1935 by salesman Charles Darrow, is known for the long hours a single game could take to complete.", "correct_answer": "Monopoly", "incorrect_answers": ["Go", "Snakes and ladders", "Sorry!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Manatees are found more commonly in Caribbean, Mexico, and Florida waters. Why?", "correct_answer": "The water is warm.", "incorrect_answers": ["The water is cool.", "There is a better food variety.", "The water is salty."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The flag of what US state features a gold torch and nineteen stars on a blue rectangular field?", "correct_answer": "Indiana", "incorrect_answers": ["Illinois", "Idaho", "Iowa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What NASA astronauts made the first untethered space walk in history in 1984?", "correct_answer": "Bruce McCandless II and Robert L. Stewart", "incorrect_answers": ["Terence T. Henricks and Bruce E. Melnick", "Aleksandr Balandin and Vladimir Dzhanibekov", "Anna Lee Fisher and Frederick D. Gregory"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Mias expectation in life in the movie The Princess Diaries?", "correct_answer": "to be invisible", "incorrect_answers": ["to live a simple life", "to be the most popular girl in school", "to be a snob"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Tonys sisters name in the movie Scarface?", "correct_answer": "Gina", "incorrect_answers": ["Nicole", "Tina", "Jen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which world denotes a phobia of a small rodent?", "correct_answer": "Musophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Technophobia", "Entomophobia", "Ophidiophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vitamin C is said to be beneficial for the treatment of various diseases and medical conditions. Which of the following is one of them?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Cancer", "AIDS", "Autism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first pitcher in major league baseball history to strike out over 3000 batters but to have less than 1000 bases on balls?", "correct_answer": "Ferguson Jenkins", "incorrect_answers": ["Don Newcombe", "Sandy Koufax", "Nolan Ryan"]}]